Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein. This
is ché for churros. Let me show you how
to make it. So to recreate the buttery
cinnamon base, we are using Fairife
milk, sweetener, salt, zantham gum, a
little bit of butter extract. Just a
splash will get you right. And then some
cinnamon. 2 to three g is all you need.
Then you can just blend that all up.
Throw it in the freezer for at least 16
hours. Then take it out, run it under
hot water for about a minute, and then
throw it in your creamy on the light ice
cream setting. Now for the mixins, these
Alpha Prime Bites cinnamon roll brownies
make the perfect churo mixin, especially
when you chop them up into little pieces
and coat them in cinnamon and sugar.
Obviously, it's not a churro. I get
that. But in terms of healthier mixin
options, this checks all the boxes. It's
packed with protein. It's chewy, but it
doesn't get soggy in the ice cream. It
has a little bit of crunch to it. It's
honestly just the perfect mixin for a
Ninja Creamy. And also, you really only
need half the brownie. I used the full
thing, but honestly, half is more than
enough. You'll still get little brownie
pieces in every single bite.